greenpageclassifieds.in 2013-03-31

# Privacy Policy | Greenpage Classifieds - Post Free Classifieds In India,Free Indian Classified Website

## Privacy Policy

**We may collect and store the following personal information:**

  1. e-mail address upon registration or upon posting a single listing on this website without creating an account. We need this For Your Contact Detail;
  2. Various information that you may include when posting a classified ad on this Website;
  3. IP address, times of access, browser type, and referring Web site addresses.

**Use of Your Information :**

Our primary purpose in collecting personal information is to provide you with a safe, smooth, efficient, and customized experience. For example, we may use your personal information and share your personal information within our corporate family to:

  1. provide the services and customer support you request, including confirming e-mails related to the Web site services, and reminders;
  2. resolve disputes, and troubleshoot problems;
  3. prevent potentially prohibited or illegal activities;
  4. customize, measure, and improve our services and the Web site’s content and layout;
  5. tell you about targeted marketing, service updates, and promotional offers based on your communication preferences;
  6. compare information for accuracy, and verify it with third parties;
  7. do other things for you as described when we collect the information;
  8. help promote a safe service;
  9. measure consumer interest in our products and services;
  10. notify you about online and offline offers, products, services, and updates;
  11. customize your experience;
  12. detect and protect us against error, fraud and other criminal activity;
  13. enforce our agreements, terms, conditions, and policies; and
  14. as otherwise described to you at the time of collection.

**Cookies.**

  * Your Information is safe with us,We may Use Cookies To Know Your Login Status .

  * We may sometimes collect some information like browser details or IP for security purposes and also those purposes which help us to provide better services to users.
  * Google-Analytics ,can use cookies to tack visitors on this website.

  * Google & Infolinks, as third party vendors, May use cookies to serve ads on our site.

  * Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet.

  * Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).
